coolsiteoftheday.com 2006-10-18

# Privacy Statement for Cool Site of the Day

C Notes Interactive, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Cool Site of the Day.

Certain forms or polls used on Cool Site of the Day may from time to time require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from these forms to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. Cool Site of the Day is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses a secure merchant account order form for visitors to submit their sites to Cool Site of the Day. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send visitors information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used  to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for services relating to the review of their submissions.

Our online surveys may from time to time ask visitors for demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, and improve on the information that we include based on our visitors responses.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our  partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss,  misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our newsletter.

You can send email to [remove@coolsiteoftheday.com](mailto:remove@coolsiteoftheday.com)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

email [info@coolsiteoftheday.com](mailto:info@coolsiteoftheday.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Michael Corso  

**WE RESPECT YOUR PRIVACY**

  * We will NEVER sell or exchange your personal information (name, e-mail address and mailing address) to anyone.
  * We will NEVER release your personal information to any other party without your express permission.
  * If we should ever give information to prospective advertisers, it is in the form of grouped statistics compiled through all our participating members' answers to survey questions. Your personal info is NOT included.
  * You may always remove yourself from any mailing lists.

Back to [Cool Site of the Day](http://www.coolsiteoftheday.com/)
